advertising365.com 2014-04-14

# Advertising365.com Affiliate Marketing Network | Terms & Conditions

_this policy covers how we protect your privacy and treat your information._

#### What This Privacy Policy Covers

This policy covers how Advertising 365 treats personal information that Advertising365 collects and receives, including information related to your past use of Advertising365 products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Advertising365 does not own or control, or to people that Advertising 365 does not employ or manage. 

#### Information Collection and Use

**General**

Advertising365 collects personal information when you register with Advertising365, when you use Advertising365 products or services, when you visit Advertising365 pages or the pages of certain Advertising365 partners. Advertising365 may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, post code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register with Advertising365 and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. Advertising365 collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of products and services that we offer. Advertising365 automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you request. Advertising365 uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

Advertising365 does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances. We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Advertising365 under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Advertising365 communicate with you about offers from Advertising365 and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Advertising 365's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. We transfer information about you if Advertising 365 is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Advertising365 will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

**Cookies**

Advertising365 may set and access Advertising365 cookies on your computer. 

**Confidentiality and Security**

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with international regulations to protect personal information about you. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Advertising365 may update this policy at any time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.
